const data = [
    {
      question: "Who's the most evil person in the dev group?",
      options: ["Nadjib", "Chakib", "Habib", "Samir"],
      correct_option: "Chakib"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the most racist person in the group?",
      options: ["Habib", "Etienne", "Tayab", "Samir"],
      correct_option: "Habib"
    },
    {
      question: "When someone new joins the group, what do we say?",
      options: [
        "How are you?",
        "What do you need?",
        "What is your position in birds?",
        "Is there a problem?"
      ],
      correct_option: "What is your position in birds?"
    },
    {
      question: "Why did Habib get banned?",
      options: [
        "Because he used the Z word",
        "Because he sent a scam",
        "Because he has a harassment picture",
        "Because the admins hate him"
      ],
      correct_option: "Because he used the Z word"
    },
    {
      question: "Why isn't Foufou allowed in the group?",
      options: [
        "Because he cannot center a div",
        "Because he published a book",
        "Because he was scared by a tube",
        "No reason"
      ],
      correct_option: "Because he was scared by a tube"
    },
    {
      question: "From the following numbers, who doesn't use Java?",
      options: ["Silas", "Nadjib", "Samir", "Tayeb"],
      correct_option: "Tayeb"
    },
    {
      question: "When Samir does something stupid, what do we say?",
      options: [
        "Nice try Samir",
        "You are kinda wrong Samir",
        "YAHDIK RABI YA SAMIR",
        "This is not the way Samir"
      ],
      correct_option: "YAHDIK RABI YA SAMIR"
    },
    {
        question: "What emoji does Samir use a lot?",
        options: ["ðŸ˜¢", "ðŸ˜„", "ðŸ¤”", "ðŸ˜ˆ"],
        correct_option: "ðŸ¤”",
      },{
      question: "You can't say you are a dev if you use:",
      options: ["Java", "React Native", "Flutter (ðŸ–•)", "Node.js"],
      correct_option: "Flutter (ðŸ–•)"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the most challenging thing you think you are forced to do:",
      options: ["Don't use ChatGPT", "Don't answer dumb questions", "Use design patterns", "Code PHP in paper"],
      correct_option: "Code PHP in paper"
    },
    {
      question: "If Nadjib says 1 + 1 = 2, what is Etienne's reply to him:",
      options: ["True", "Obviously", "Totally wrong", "Totally right"],
      correct_option: "Totally wrong"
    },
    {
      question: "Why did Dev DZ kick the gang:",
      options: ["They were skilled", "They were toxic", "They insulted people", "They said you should use Flutter"],
      correct_option: "They were skilled"
    },
    {
      question: "Among these people, who doesn't eat liver:",
      options: ["Nadjib", "Chakib", "Etienne", "Tayeb"],
      correct_option: "Etienne"
    },
    {
      question: "GTA is a crime game that Samir plays, so he:",
      options: ["Kills people (ðŸ”ª)", "Robs banks (ðŸ’°)", "Drives (ðŸš—)", "Fights gangs (ðŸ’€)"],
      correct_option: "Drives (ðŸš—)"
    },
    {
      question: "What does the 'L' stand for in SOLID:",
      options: ["Liskov Substitution Principle", "Logical Code Organization", "Long Functionality Principle", "Lazy Initialization Principle"],
      correct_option: "Liskov Substitution Principle"
    },
  ];
  
  export default data;
  